Welcome back!
欢迎回来！
This is your first Stoppr lesson
这是你的第一节Stoppr课程
We are covering an important topic today.
今天我们将讨论一个重要话题。
Where is sugar hiding.
糖藏在哪里。
My name is Emma.
我叫艾玛。
Let's get started!
让我们开始吧！
Here's a funny story.
这是一个有趣的故事。
Sugar actually sneaks into foods you would never expect.
糖其实会偷偷溜进你意想不到的食物中。
The goal is to identify those foods.
目标是识别这些食物。
When you will know about those, you can reduce the amount you
当你了解这些后，你可以减少摄入量。
eat every day.
每天吃。
Or, you can replace them completely with something else.
或者，你可以完全用其他东西替代它们。
Your main mission is to get to a weekly mix that is good for
你的主要任务是达到一个对
your body, and for your everyday energy.
你的身体和日常能量有益的每周组合。
Let's discover this, together.
让我们一起发现这个。
Number 1.
第一。
Sauces and dressings.
酱料和调味汁。
Things like ketchup, barbecue sauce, salad dressings.
像番茄酱、烧烤酱、沙拉调料这样的东西。
Even the sauce you add to your pasta.
甚至是你加到意大利面的酱。
It's basically all the industrial foods.
基本上所有的工业食品都是这样。
They all have sugar added, to taste better.
它们都添加了糖，以便味道更好。
But it's not good for you.
但这对你不好。
It get's you tired, and addicted.
它让你感到疲惫，并且上瘾。
Like a bad drug.
就像一种不好的毒品。
Always check the label, at the back of any industrial product,
始终检查任何工业产品背面的标签，
to see the quantity of sugar it contains.
查看它所含的糖分量。
Check the Carbo-hydrates line, it's the sugar line basically.
查看碳水化合物这一行，基本上就是糖的含量。
For foods, if there's more than 5% of Carbo-hydrates, it's too
对于食物，如果碳水化合物超过5%，就太多了。
much.
太多了。
For drinks, if it's more than 3% of Carbo-hydrates, it's too
对于饮料来说，如果碳水化合物含量超过3%，就太
much.
多了。
You will see that a lot of the industrial food has a lot of sugar.
你会发现很多工业食品含有大量的糖。
But that's ok.
但没关系。
In a future lesson.
在未来的课程中。
We will discover other foods, that taste the same, but don't
我们将发现其他味道相同但糖分较少的食物。
have as much sugar.
含糖量。
Now let's see the groups of foods that can really hide sugar.
现在让我们看看那些真正隐藏糖分的食物类别。
Dairy products.
乳制品。
Flavored yogurts, chocolate milk, and creamy desserts often have
调味酸奶、巧克力牛奶和奶油甜点通常含有
lots of sugar.
大量的糖。
To cut down, try plain yogurt or milk and add fresh fruit for
为了减少摄入量，尝试使用原味酸奶或牛奶，并添加新鲜水果
sweetness.
来增加甜味。
Another group.
另一个类别。
Bread.
面包。
Bread that say "healthy" or "whole grain" can still have lots of
标有“健康”或“全谷物”的面包仍然可能含有大量
sugar.
糖。
Try to cut down on eating bread, as much as possible, even if it
尽量减少吃面包，即使它
seems low sugar.
看起来糖分低。
Another one.
再来一个。
Pasta.
意大利面。
Pasta itself contains hidden sugar.
意大利面本身含有隐藏的糖分。
It's sometimes added during production to improve the texture, the taste.
有时在生产过程中会加入糖以改善质地和口感。
Even plain pasta might contain sugar.
即使是普通的意大利面也可能含有糖。
Check the label to choose pasta without added sugars.
查看标签，选择不含添加糖的意大利面。
But really, try to reduce your consumption of any pasta - it's
但实际上，尽量减少任何意大利面的摄入 - 这
easier in the end.
最终会更容易。
Another one.
又来一个。
Fruits have natural sugar, which is fine when eaten whole.
水果含有天然糖分，整个食用是没问题的。
But dried or canned fruits often have extra sugar added.
但干果或罐装水果通常会添加额外的糖分。
Fresh fruit is the better choice.
新鲜水果是更好的选择。
There we go!
就这样！
That's already a lot of information.
这已经是很多信息了。
I think we are good for today.
我觉得我们今天就到这里。
If you already apply those tips, you can go a long way.
如果你已经应用这些建议，你会走得很远。
In future lessons, We will find how to replace those sugary foods,
在未来的课程中，我们将找到如何替换那些含糖食物的方法，
don't worry.
别担心。
I'm happy that you're taking the good steps to remove sugar from
我很高兴你正在采取积极的步骤来去除生活中的糖分。
your life.
你的生活。
I wish you a wonderful day, and hope to see you in a future lesson!
祝你有美好的一天，希望在以后的课程中见到你！
See you soon!
很快再见！